# Paulo Corrêa

Uberlândia, Minas Gerais, Brazil



henriqueph@hotmail.com



linkedin.com/in/henriqueph

### Summary

Computer analyst and programmer, passionate about technology. Took part in many projetcs using C#, Java, VBA, JS, Oracle, MySQL, SQL Server, and others. I have worked in many Fiscal and Finantial Projects, such as 'SPED Fiscal', 'Sped Contribuições', 'NFe', 'CTe', and others. Also worked on several projects using Javascript, JQuery, NodeJs, MongoDb, and React, at the University of Toronto as a student.

#### **Experience**



#### Java / VBA / MySQL / C# Programmer

PHMR Informática

Apr 2016 - Present (4 years 7 months +)

## Finantial / IT Business Analyst

Avon

Oct 2008 - Mar 2016 (7 years 6 months)

#### **Education**



#### Udemy Alumni

Software Development, 2020 2020 - 2020

JQuery, Java EE, PHP, and MySQL.

## University of Toronto

Full-Stack Web Development 2020 - 2020

#### Universidade Ibirapuera

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 1999 - 2003

#### Skills

Java • JavaScript • SPED Fiscal/Contribuições • C# • Express.js • Node.js • MySQL • PL/SQL · Node Express · React.js